Getting a Lesson in the Education of Japanese University Students
See, to an adult.
Yes, sir
Yes, sir!
It's finished!
Dumpling
This is a facial tissue.
So cute!
See you soon.
Good morning.
I just finished my hair and makeup.
Cute
Oh, this is nice. It's okay, right?
Costume fee for the new costume tour
Hair ornaments. Cute.
I got the pack.
Here we are.
Bye.
Hello.
I just finished my makeup.
I'm wearing half-twin today.
They're so cute.
Here, we'll wear catsuits.
That's right, we're wearing catsuits today.
So let's makeover together.
Let's go!
Ready?
Here we go.
Bye-bye!
bye bye
please
Good morning
Ta-da!
Good morning.
Wholesale.
Over here.
The hair ornament for the new costume.
I really wanted to wear this charade, so I asked my stylist.
Cute as hair.
The bangs will go into the kime a little later.
Good night.
I got a dumpling!
Take your rice and eat it!
me
ha
sheets
I want you first
You dumped me and I want you first
That's the character of a maiden
She wants to see the soil.
It's from a friend.
You dumped me and I'm the prettiest of the prettiest
You're supposed to be the most flirtatious with me
I'm the cutest of the cutest
Come on, Shuker, Shoemaker, Shoemaker, Shoemaker.
Kukkowar, I'm in tears
♪ So messy, so pretty ♪
I liked you so much.
You broke up with me.
Come on, it's the cutest thing I've ever seen
That's the character of a maiden
She said, "Show me the dirt.
She said she's as pretty as she loves
Schuenger.
This is the damsel in distress
You dumped me and I'm the prettiest of the prettiest
You're supposed to be the most flirtatious with me
I've never seen that before.
Yes, I have.
You've never seen it before.
I don't talk to people that much.
My heart's pounding.
It won't go away even if you trust me.
I love you
I'll sing it in Kanamizu Shinme
That's what it's come to
If it goes this far...
I might not be able to sell it
Bang.
I'm sorry I couldn't speak up today
I'll dance with a big smile and a lot of energy.
Everybody, please speak up to the hurdles...okay?
Okay, one more time.
All right.
Ewars.
Prepare'd
If you're Theres
anız
I got the translation function
I'm going to two countries.
Thank you so much!
Super useful!
It's the best!
You can speak very well.
Pocket Talk?
Ah, here he is. Oharuchi.
Look, I got the translation function.
Wow, that's great.
Oharu, can we do this today?
Is it going to be in English? From Japanese.
Oh, I see. I have to start speaking.
What's the point? Oharu is using the translation function.
I'm curious about the fact that she speaks in Korean, too.
Amazing.
Oharu, oharu.
The last room before the halfway house.
Finished fixing my makeup.
Your bangs are beautiful with a bang.
How are you today?
How's your day?
Please!
Yellow and blue.
Yellow and blue are so cute!
Heh heh heh.
I did my best
Here we are, we did our best!
We had lunch
Lunch lunch lunch lunch
Delicious
Arrangement
Ah!
Maybe if we get a little closer, we can go there.
Camera.
Yeah, and...
Fix it.
I'll do my best.
Monster.
Canavi, something like that. I went in with my hands.
I tried to go backstage, but they said no.
They said no.
I think they're changing.
There's a bit of a line.
I don't know.
This tour is very close to the fans.
Lots of free time for recording... a little bit longer version.
I hope they look cute in the pictures.
I hope it will look good on camera or cell phone.
After singing a lot, everyone is going to be so close
I don't want to look like a mess.
Please be gentle.
Oh, man, I'm sweating.
My bangs are done.
Oh my God, I can't do my bangs today.
I don't know what to do.
I borrow your light, ladies and gentlemen.
A little bit of junk can go a long way.
Did I say one-sided?
I'm off!
I'll sing today.
Good night
Good night.
I said "tiki".
Did you? Yes, I did.
I said yes tiki afterwards, and I always say it just in case.
This is a special version.
I only do it when Hito-chan does it.
If I don't do it, I don't do it.
It's up to me.
I will do it on that day.
Thank you for your hard work.
It was fun.
I'm glad you had fun with the flowers too.
It's been going on for 1,000 yen to the flowers.
It was fun.
That's the abbreviation for maiden.
Well then, the first day in Osaka is over.
Thank you very much.
The summer tour has started next, hasn't it?
Mr. Uemi, on the first day, I was wondering if we were really going to perform today,
I was of course happy at first when the show started.
Until now, until now.
Sing this song with me.
It's true.
Everyone loves songs that make life worth living.
A snack.
Sure, some songs we haven't played in a while.
And there were.
And it was so much fun.
Man-made costumes.
Here we are.
It's been a while since I've worn this costume.
I've never seen you here before, but you came a lot.
So cute.
So cute. The costumes.
The first and second costumes are both cute.
We can connect them to the future.
By all means, let's make a live concert.
By all means.
We will deliver them to the whole world with this tour.
We will deliver it.
Next stop is Korea.
Korea on tour.
Everyone has always wanted to go to Korea,
We've been playing with them privately and so on,
I've been having a lot of fun in my private life, but I wanted to go to Korea for the whole concert,
I've been drinking a little bit more.
I thought it wasn't quite ready yet,
I'm going to Korea in two weeks.
I hope everyone will prepare well for the Korean tour so that everyone in Korea and those coming to Korea from Japan can look forward to seeing us,
I will do my best, everyone!
Thank you very much for the Osaka concert!
Yes, I'll be there.
This way?
Here we go.
Look at these eyelashes!
Look at those eyelashes. - They're cute.
Cute, huh?
Half up.
They're cute.
They're so cute.
Oh, look at the sparkles!
Did you get a cute shot of the recording free time?
Let me buzz you.
I'll give you one of my own just for you.
I'd love it if you'd give it a little lift.
Next stop: Korea
This is the last of the 22chai!
Look, 22chai guys!
Next up is 23 Chai, and we're going to perform in Korea!
Next time, 23 Chai, bye-bye!
Thank you very much for the Osaka show!
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching